there are many powerful Gods in Egyptian
mythology Anubis the God of the Dead
Horus the God of the sky the winged
dragon of raw God of the Sun but
probably the more important of them all
the God
Bartleby Montclair of Dresden the God of
sexiness it is commonly believed that
the Pharaohs are the only ones on earth
who can make contact with these Gods
while many don't believe this to be true
that it's some form of hoax
there was one Pharaoh from ancient Egypt
who can swear on his life that it is
true because he has not only met with
many of the Gods but he's even had but
sex with the God
Bartleby quite a few times during his
reign as Pharaoh this is the story of
the Pharaoh that time forgot Sonic the
Hedgehog
chapter 1 a lonely night it was late at
night as Sonic sat atop his throne he
had a long busy day beating slaves and
watching the pyramids be built in his
honor right now he was relieving himself
of his stress by writing a steamy
fanfiction about him and the God of
sexiness Bartleby Sonic tries to keep it
hidden that he has feelings for the God
because he knows that it is a forbidden
love the people of Egypt all know about
it however they won't say anything
because they all agree that Sonic and
Bartleby made quite a cute couple that
and if any of them did say anything
Sonic would use his power and ferret to
kill them Sonic just about to write the
sex scene of his fanfic when he heard
the chambers to his throne room open in
Kain his siblings Manic and Sonya they
both looked exhausted they must have run
all the way here through the desert of
King's Sonic thought Sonya Manic my two
siblings what is going on that you had
to come here I'm such agency Sonia asked
its Bartleby Sonic
it's fartole be he descended from the
Heavens and started killing people
Sonya cried like a Sonic couldn't
believe what he heard Bartleby his lover
would never do such a thing he is a kind
and beautiful God that everybody looked
up to
it's true bro Maddox said tears running
down his own face Bartleby has become
evil he always killed mom and Uncle
Chuck Sonic became furious you're lying
Sonic screamed punching Manic in the
face Manic fell to the ground with a
bloody nose you're lying to me
Bartleby would never do such a thing
Sonic's hands turned into another fist
really to punch Manic in the face once
more but Sonia spoke up Sonic please
believe us
Sonic cried before she could say
anything else
Sonic slapped here across the face she
too fell to the floor you may be my
sister but I am the Pharaoh here
you only get to speak when I tell you to
Sonic said asserting his dominance
to his sibs Sonic walked past them but
not before kicking Manic in the face
once more and slapping his butt cheeks
to make sure his bro knew his place if
Bartleby really is killing the people of
Egypt then I believe he is doing it for
a reason he is a God after all my God my
my lover Sonia and mattock were shocked
at what they hear Dada they can W Sonic
dreams aboot bernal be all the time and
they even know that they have butt sex
in secret but nobody could have ever
expected that Sonic and Bartleby were
actually lovers Sonic wasn't going to
hide his feelings for the sexy blonde
man anymore
it was time for the world to know about
their love Sonic exited the throne room
in search of Bartleby chapter 2 the
truth
Sonic ran through the desert sands
towards the town where he heard screams
the only light that illuminated the
sands were he stars in the sky Sonic
always likes stars they made him think
about how sparkly Barnaby's butt cheeks
look when they're all sweaty after a
workout it didn't take long for him to
get to the town and when he did he saw
exactly what his sips had warned him
about right in front of him was Bartleby
beating the living out of a man
when Bartleby noticed Sonic he quit
used his Godlike powers to set the man
on fire immediately the man turned to
ashes
Sonic blushed Bartleby looked so so cool
and and so manly Sonic licked his lips
in lust
Bartleby what's going on while you are
killing people
Sonic asked Bartleby made his way over
to Sonic got to his knees so that his
was at eye level with Sonic and slapped
the Hedgehogs jiggly but Bartleby
said I'm glad you are alright and with
that Bartleby pulled Sonic into an
embrace Sonic was caught off guard as
Bartleby squeezed his right butt cheek
like one would squeeze lemon juice out
of a plump lemon
what do you mean Bartleby of course I'm
all right
Sonic said while blushing you don't get
it do you my Bart would be asked
Sonic shook his head the slaves were
planning an attack on you Bartleby said
as a God I know I wasn't supposed to
intervene with human Athairs but I
couldn't just sit there and watch you
die Oh Bartleby Sonic wiped a tear from
his eye you did all this to save me
thank you thank you Bartleby I love you
I love you with all my heart
Sonic wrapped his arm around his lover
Bartleby smiled come how about we
head back to your throne room and have a
little fun Bartleby asked Sonic blushed
like a you you mean
like butt sex Sonic asked shyly Bartleby
giggled